Conor Lamb

Customer Success Engineer | Web Developer







portfolio-conorl11.vercel.app

SUMMARY

Technical expert with 6 years of client facing experience and web development experience. Uses a combination of programming expertise, and top notch customer support to assist clients with software implementations focused on complex solutions, integrations, data automations, custom dashboards, and the development of custom utilities and web applications.

Skills

Javascript SQL CSS HTML Angular APIs Node React Redux Redux Toolkit Dashboarding Data Visualization Data Modeling Google Visualization Plotly UI / UX Design Agile

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Senior Implementation Specialist (Contract / Part Time)

DEC 2023 - Current

Revalize (formerly Configure One)

Remote

- Mentors and trains junior team members on solution design, CPQ best practices, and client relation skills
- Provides tier 3 support for the highest complexity and priority issues for the Configure One product

Customer Success Engineer / Technical Success Manager

AUG 2021 - DEC 2023

Quantive

Remote

- Instructed customer base (including multiple Fortune 500 companies) on all technical features of the platform, including Quantive's Artificial Intelligence (AI) features
- Designed and developed the most visited and highly utilized dashboard across all Quantive clients
- Developed, designed, and provided ongoing maintenance of 300+ insights and dashboards in application marketplace
- Built custom integrations to pull data across a software stack into the Quantive Platform
- Automated KPIs and Key Results using advanced SQL queries against the Quantive Database
- Created custom visualizations ranging from widgets to interactive full page web applications with multiple click paths
- Developed and maintained web application allowing Customer Success to easily transfer data across multiple accounts
- Maintained a Node app that uses REST APIs to provide customers with an Excel import/export product feature
- Updated and maintained VSCode Extension allowing for improved custom development within Quantive Platform

Senior CPQ Implementation Consultant / Implementation Consultant

JAN 2018 - AUG 2021

Configure One (now Revalize)

Chicago, IL

- Partnered with SMEs at manufacturing companies to build UIs allowing them to more effectively sell complex products
- Collaborated with NetSuite and Salesforce partners to integrate CPQ solutions to ERP and CRM softwares
- Managed multiple implementation projects from kick-off to go-live for Configure Price Quote (CPQ) software

Personal Projects

MeadFantasyFootball.com

DEC 2023 - Feb 2024

- Designed and coded website to visualize Fantasy Football data in user friendly and fun formats
- Performed ETL operations with the ESPN and Sleeper APIs to pull data from multiple sources into MongoDB
- Utilized Mongo, Express, React, and Node (MERN Stack) to build data models visualize them with advanced CSS

EDUCATION

Purdue University

DEC 2017

Bachelor of Science: Industrial Engineering

West Lafayette, IN

- Designed GUI for a Smart Fridge and integrated SQLQueries to provide information to customers
- Used R Studio functions to scrape data from hockeyreference.com for a statistical analysis on performance indicators

INTERESTS

Basketball

Dance Music

Sitcoms

Snowboarding

Camping

Sci Fi and Fantasy Novels

Purdue Sports